{
    "id": "6bad75c9ee3a441ba1cead1667847199",
    "title": "Sentence Synthesis Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "........................................ he is snobbish, I like him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "But",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Both my mother .......................................... father attended the wedding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has walked five miles, ...................................... he must be tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the shop ......................................... bought a watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must be quiet .................................... you must leave the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The prisoner fell down on his knees ........................................... begged for mercy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "as well"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... I left home early, I could not get to work on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Even if",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Kabir works harder ......................................... Azim.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must start at once .......................................... you will be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "but",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know ..................................... you are not interested in this offer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}